<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<collctibles>
    <collectible id = "1">
        <collectibleSentence> ORIGINS: Heir of the notorious Nobel family, Markus was among the bast hacker-slaves at disposal of DoesBreez’yo. He helped in the construction of the simulated reality prison hoping to one day restore the name of his prestigious family, so to have - in his head – the right to be even sassier to whoever. Overhearing a conversation between the regime high-ranks, Markus finally understood that once the Squashes will be done with the planet exploitation, Earth will be destroyed. For him this meant just one thing… no one to brag his noble Nobel status with! Unacceptable!     IMPRISONMENT: With his heart in a mixture of hate and superb disappointment, he decided to fly from the tyrant stronghold and try to restore his family name with his own hands, with the only means he knew: hacking! After a period passed training his skill inserting typos and adding moustaches to the e-propaganda billboards, he decided to finally act on a larger scale attack: replace al the billboards with old clips of Nobel nominations. Sadly, the regime techniques were too much even for him and the location of the origin of the attack was soon discovered. He was immediately captured and imprisoned, to be soon executed for high treason
        </collectibleSentence>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id = "2"> <collectibleSentence>ORIGINS:Born and raised in the last Sicilian bakery family, Ken became DoesBreez’yo’s personal baker after proving himself to be the only one capable of baking the Glorious Cannolo of Tardigrades. His kind heart was though not satisfied with the famine situation suffered by the population, so he habitually sneaked leftovers from the tyrant kitchen for the starving population - and for his own personal taste of course! IMPRISONMENT: His kindness was only equalled by his gluttony: he loved to share as much as he loved to eat. During an hunger strike he crawled to the tyrant’s kitchen and begun a huge banquet of whatever he could find. On the edge of his crisis, with the mouth still full, his eyes fell on one of his famous Glorious Cannolos. As he touched the state-of-the-art dessert, though, the alien forces blasted through the door to seize him. He was imprisoned on the spot, for stealing to the king and trying to waste precious Tardigrades.</collectibleSentence>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id = "3">
        <collectibleSentence>ORIGINS: Head of the Squash Propaganda Department, Kam falls inevitably falls victim of alcoholism because of the unsatisfaction the job gives to her artistic spirit. Unable to hold back her creativity, Kam finds shelter for her art in the needs of the resistance:  in addition to the secret art expositions she always took part in, she became a vivid exponent of the counterpropaganda.     IMPRISONMENT: One night, she was caught in the worst timing possible: she was discovered totally naked, covered in paint while drunkenly painting DoesBreez’yo french-kissing a tardigrade. She tried to escape throwing paint buckets and barf projectiles to the alien police, but her efforts were useless. Se was seized and locked up for iconoclasm. </collectibleSentence>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id = "4">
        <collectibleSentence>ORIGINS: Orphaned when he was just a child, Raphael was taken in custody by the clerics of the Squash New Church: the cult of the regime that wiped out all the old religions to indoctrinate the slaves in the veneration of the tyrant DoesBreez’yo. Despite his love for knowledge and his great wisdom, Raphael has always had a young and jokester spirit: he loves to pull pranks to his fellow clerics.     IMPRISONMENT: One day, though, he pulled the clerics’ strings too hard: he stole a furry vest used only by the high clerics for particular celebrations and dressed up as a huge space monkey. He then sneaked up in the sanctuary during a mess and exclaimed “I’m the almighty Sas-squash! Yield before my magnificent fur!”. The clerics did not enjoy the prank as he expected: they called the authorities who brought him away. He was charged with supreme blasphemy and imprisoned. </collectibleSentence>
    </collectible>
</collctibles>